[Music]
This poem is a government organization ICICI
Lombard company office District
Agriculture Officer Assurance - Share Loss
wrong
that Chitrana Pic Insurance lazy festival
organization AISA workers have broken the
enemy movement for the company office Companies did
not give money from education The
organization has given the signal
that the first independent first successful
experiment of drone in Palghar district Karna Kala Jawahar
Circle Inaccessible tribal areas Bhagat
worship orphanage place at Rajiv Gandhi Stadium
This primary school or from a big state
Principal Secretary of Health Department Pradeep Vyas is
present and drone inch ad wheat
17 km interval Asalya where
primary health camera source goes
Good Wife